viralblog.com 2019-03-16

# Privacy Policy |

#### Sign-up to get the content you like

* * *

Our readers can personalize ViralBlog in Zite alike ways, and **schedule e-mail alerts** to get the most relevant answers to their specific questions.

**Choose your sign-up method:**

Could not connect to Twitter. Refresh the page or try again later.

* * *

By signing-up you agree upon our terms and conditions

Last Updated on: October 10, 2012

ViralBlog is committed to protecting the privacy of visitors to our website, subscribers to our newsletters, members of our forum and those providing contact information. In addition, ViralBlog is opposed to unauthorized commercial e-mail delivery, otherwise known as spam.  
Please read the following Privacy and Spam Policy to understand how your personal information is treated.

**WHAT INFORMATION DO WE COLLECT?** ViralBlog only collects user-provided personally identifiable information. This information is provided when website visitors complete one of our online forms (examples include newsletter subscriptions or contact forms). The following list includes ways we collect personal information from our website visitors and the type of information collected:

**ELECTRONIC NEWSLETTER:** To register online for our electronic newsletter, we request the following required information: (i) name, and (ii) e-mail address. The provision of this information is mandatory in order to receive our newsletter.

**CONTACT FORMS:** To contact ViralBlog for the purposes of evaluating or engaging our services or to answer your questions, we utilize numerous forms throughout our site. Required information varies depending on the form and at most includes (i) name, and (ii) e-mail address. The provision of this information is mandatory in order to receive a response. The provision of the remaining information requested on the registration form is optional.

**DOES VIRALBLOG SHARE MY INFORMATION?** No, ViralBlog will not share, rent or sell your personally identifiable information with third parties.

**HOW DOES VIRALBLOG USE MY INFORMATION?** Personal information and settings collected by ViralBlog are used primarily for the purpose of personalization of the blog and scheduling the e-mail alerts that are relevant for you. Our membership and personal info are used to recognize you and to enable you to comment on stories fast and easy.

**HOW CAN I OPT OUT?** If you have opted in and later desire to opt-out from further receiving the ViralBlog newsletter, you can make this change at any time by clicking on the unsubscribe URL embedded in our newsletter.

**SPAM POLICY:** ViralBlog is strongly opposed to spam. We will only send e-mail to users that have explicitly requested to receive our newsletter or personalized e-mail alerts.

**WEB LINKS:** This web site contains links to other sites. Please be aware that ViralBlog is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site to read the privacy and spam policies of each and every web site that collects personally identifiable information. This Privacy and Spam Policy applies solely to information collected by this web site.

**HOW DO I CONTACT VIRALBLOG:** If you have any further questions or comments regarding the ViralBlog website or this Privacy and Spam Policy, you may [contact us here](http://www.viralblog.com/contact/ "Contact Page").

**LEGAL DISCLAIMER:** We may disclose personal information when required by law or in the good-faith belief that such action is necessary in order to conform to the edicts of the law or comply with a legal process served on our site.
